<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WWU Cybersecurity Club</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on WWU Cybersecurity Club</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright 2019 WWU Cybersecurity Club</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 12:35:48 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>October Survey</title><link>/posts/october-survey/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 12:35:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/october-survey/</guid><description>Loading…</description></item><item><title>Sign Up for the Club Newsletter</title><link>/posts/sign-up-for-the-club-newsletter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 18:59:23 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/sign-up-for-the-club-newsletter/</guid><description>This form is now closed after the 2019 info fair. To get on our mailing list, shoot us a message at cscwwu at gmail.com
Loading…</description></item><item><title>Calendar</title><link>/calendar/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 15:20:10 -0700</pubDate><guid>/calendar/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Resources</title><link>/resources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 20:28:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>/resources/</guid><description>Blogs &amp;amp; News Krebs on Security Cisco Talos Arstechnica Daniel Miessler Phoronix Wired Ycombinator HackerNews
Programming and Computer Science Programming Codecademy Learn You a Haskell Computer Science and Operating Systems Operating Systems: Three Easy Pieces Computer Networks: A Systems Approach Resource Dumps What Every CS Student Should Know Open Source Computer Science Degree Curated Programming Resources OWASP Security Cheatsheet Tools &amp;amp; Other Markdown Tutorial Github Git Handbook The Git Book (overkill for beginners) Vimtutor: If you&amp;rsquo;ve installed vim, simply run vimtutor in your shell</description></item><item><title>How to Edit This Site</title><link>/posts/how-to-edit-this-site/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 20:46:05 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/how-to-edit-this-site/</guid><description>This site is created using the Hugo static site generator. Hugo accepts Markdown and translates it into HTML/CSS/JS based on the provided theme. This site uses the terminal theme. Terminal has some theme-specific features, which are detailed in the previous link.
How to build this site: Firstly, make sure that you&amp;rsquo;re using a recent version of Hugo. The version shipped in Debian stable is too old for our purposes. The author is using v0.</description></item><item><title>Western Washington University Cybersecurity Club</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 18:22:03 -0700</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>Welcome to the Cybersecurity Club! We&amp;rsquo;re looking forward to having a great year in 2019 &amp;amp; 2020. Check out the calendar page for our future activities.
Our plans for this year include:
* Capture-the-Flag competitions and CCDC practice
* CCNA and networking study sessions
* Creating virtual testing environments on top of physical hardware
* Trips to visit security companies &amp;amp; teams
* Internship and job-seeking guidance, resume reviews, etc</description></item></channel></rss>