<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WWU Cybersecurity Club</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on WWU Cybersecurity Club</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright 2021 WWU Cybersecurity Club</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 20:46:05 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Edit This Site</title>
      <link>/posts/how-to-edit-this-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 20:46:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/how-to-edit-this-site/</guid>
      <description>This site is created using the Hugo static site generator. Hugo accepts Markdown and translates it into HTML/CSS/JS based on the provided theme. This site uses the terminal theme. Terminal has some theme-specific features, which are detailed in the previous link.
How to build this site: Firstly, make sure that you&amp;rsquo;re using a recent version of Hugo. The version shipped in Debian stable is too old for our purposes. The author is using v0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calendar</title>
      <link>/calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/calendar/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/</guid>
      <description>Blogs &amp;amp; News  Krebs on Security Cisco Talos Kayne McGladrey Arstechnica Daniel Miessler Phoronix Ycombinator HackerNews
  Programming and Computer Science: Tutorials and Resources Programming  Codecademy Learn You a Haskell  Computer Science and Operating Systems  Operating Systems: Three Easy Pieces Computer Networks: A Systems Approach Linux Academy (requires a (free) account)  Resource Dumps  What Every CS Student Should Know Open Source Computer Science Degree Curated Programming Resources OWASP Security Cheatsheet  Security  Portswigger Academy (Webapp Pentesting)  Cloud  AWS Training  Tools &amp;amp; Other  Markdown Tutorial Github Git Handbook The Git Book (overkill for beginners) Vimtutor: If you&amp;rsquo;ve installed vim, simply run vimtutor in your shell</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Western Washington University Cybersecurity Club</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Cybersecurity Club! We&amp;rsquo;re looking forward to having a great year in 2020 &amp;amp; 2021. Check out the calendar page for our future activities.
Our plans for this year include:
* Capture-the-Flag competitions and CCDC practice
* CCNA and networking study sessions
* Creating virtual testing environments on top of physical hardware
* Trips to visit security companies &amp;amp; teams
* Internship and job-seeking guidance, resume reviews, etc</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>