<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WWU Cybersecurity Club</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on WWU Cybersecurity Club</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright 2019 WWU Cybersecurity Club</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 15:20:10 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Calendar</title><link>/calendar/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 15:20:10 -0700</pubDate><guid>/calendar/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Resources</title><link>/resources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 20:28:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>/resources/</guid><description> Google CTF 2019 Resources Google: Main Page CTF Time: Google CTF 2017 Challenges and Writeups List Google: Github Repo with Solutions Bernie Lim: Beginner&amp;rsquo;s Quest Jack Halon: Beginner&amp;rsquo;s Quest CTF Resources CTF Time CBT Nuggets: How to Prepare For a CTF Competition Cybrary: CTF Introduction (useful links at the bottom) Youtube LiveOverflow: What is CTF? Trail of Bits: CTF Field Guide Google: Writeups from previous CTFs Blogs Krebs on Security Cisco Talos Arstechnica Daniel Miessler Phoronix Wired Ycombinator HackerNews Various Learning Challenges Cryptopals: Crypto Implementation Project Euler: Math and logic challenges XSS Games: Cross-site scripting challenges Free Stuff for Students JetBrains software licenses Github Student Developer Pack Azure Student Credit</description></item><item><title>How to Edit This Site</title><link>/posts/how-to-edit-this-site/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 20:46:05 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/how-to-edit-this-site/</guid><description>This site is created using the Hugo static site generator. Hugo accepts Markdown and translates it into HTML/CSS/JS based on the provided theme. This site uses the terminal theme. Terminal has some theme-specific features, which are detailed in the previous link.
How to build this site: Firstly, make sure that you&amp;rsquo;re using a recent version of Hugo. The version shipped in Debian stable is too old for our purposes. The author is using v0.</description></item><item><title>Western Washington University Cybersecurity Club</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 18:22:03 -0700</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>Welcome to the WWU Cybersecurity Club! Links Our Github
Our Slack
WWU Cybersecurity Department</description></item></channel></rss>