<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on WWU Cybersecurity Club</title><link>/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on WWU Cybersecurity Club</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright 2019 WWU Cybersecurity Club</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 21:01:07 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tempered Networks Visit Sign-Up</title><link>/posts/tempered-networks-visit-sign-up/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 21:01:07 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/tempered-networks-visit-sign-up/</guid><description>Our visit to Tempered Networks in Seattle will take place the afternoon of Thursday, November 7th. We will depart Seattle at approximately noon, spend two hours with Tempered, and eat dinner in Seattle before returning to Bellingham (don&amp;rsquo;t worry about the cost- dinner is on us!)
We will be arranging carpools to Seattle. If you need to skip lunch and return to Bellingham immediately after our visit to Tempered, please mention this in the sign-up form and we will make it happen.</description></item><item><title>October Survey</title><link>/posts/october-survey/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 12:35:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/october-survey/</guid><description>Loading…</description></item><item><title>Sign Up for the Club Newsletter</title><link>/posts/sign-up-for-the-club-newsletter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 18:59:23 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/sign-up-for-the-club-newsletter/</guid><description>This form is now closed after the 2019 info fair. To get on our mailing list, shoot us a message at cscwwu at gmail.com
Loading…</description></item><item><title>How to Edit This Site</title><link>/posts/how-to-edit-this-site/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 20:46:05 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/how-to-edit-this-site/</guid><description>This site is created using the Hugo static site generator. Hugo accepts Markdown and translates it into HTML/CSS/JS based on the provided theme. This site uses the terminal theme. Terminal has some theme-specific features, which are detailed in the previous link.
How to build this site: Firstly, make sure that you&amp;rsquo;re using a recent version of Hugo. The version shipped in Debian stable is too old for our purposes. The author is using v0.</description></item></channel></rss>